Finding Aid for the Howard Morehead photographs and papers PASC-M.0142
UCLA Library Special Collections
Howard Morehead photographs and papers
circa 1940-2002
UCLA Library Special Collections
Morehead, Howard
PASC-M.0142
10.8 linear feet (12 boxes, 4 shoe boxes, 6 flat boxes, 3 oversize flat boxes)
Howard Morehead was a photographer, broadcast news cameraman, and impresario. A native of Topeka, Kansas, he moved to Los Angeles after World War II and joined the staff of the Los Angeles Sentinel and did freelance work for a number of magazines. He also founded the Miss Bronze California beauty pageant as a reaction to the systematic discrimination faced by African American women. The collection consists predominantly of photographs of musicians and venues documenting the Los Angeles jazz scene from the mid-1950s through the 1990s. There are also a number of actors and politicians represented. There is a very large amount of glamour photography featuring models and beauty pageant contestants. Some personal and business papers are also present, as well as books, videotapes, and sound recordings from Morehead's personal collection.
Conditions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
RESTRICTED ACCESS: Use of audiovisual material requires production of listening copies.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
CONTAINS DIGITAL/AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: This collection contains processed [digital/audiovisual] materials. All requests to access digital materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Howard Morehead, 2003.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9953315513606533
Biography
Howard Morehead was born in Topeka, Kansas in 1926. After graduating from high school, he enlisted in the Army Air Corps and was assigned to Tuskegee Army Airfield, where he began training as a pilot in anticipation of joining the pioneering Tuskegee Airmen. The war ended before he saw combat, and after his discharge from the military he moved to Los Angeles.
After earning a degree in photography from Los Angeles City College, he joined the staff of the Los Angeles Sentinel newspaper in 1950, and also freelanced for various magazines. Eventually he became the first West Coast staff photographer for Johnson Publishing Company, contributing stories and covers for Ebony and Jet. A fan of jazz music, Morehead photographed many of the important musicians of his time, as well as many actors and politicians.
His interest in glamour photography and his awareness of racial discrimination inspired him to found the Miss Bronze L.A. beauty contest in 1958, which soon expanded into the Miss Bronze California pageant, affording African American women the opportunity to compete. In 1970, Morehead became the first African American hired as a staff cameraman for a Los Angeles television station when he began working for KTLA. After a year, he moved to KABC, where he spent seventeen years as a cameraman before retiring.
Morehead continued to document the Los Angeles jazz scene throughout the 1990s. He died in July, 2003.
Scope and Content
The collection predominantly consists of photographs taken by Morehead, mostly of musicians and venues in Los Angeles from the mid-1950s through the 1990s. Subjects include Ray Charles, Miles Davis, Billie Holiday, and many others. There are also a number of actors and politicians represented, including Diahann Carroll, Redd Foxx, John F. Kennedy, and Martin Luther King, Jr. Many of the most important photographs from Morehead's early career exist only as a single image. For instance, there is one photograph of Dexter Gordon that Morehead clearly favored and replicated numerous times in different contexts. But there is no negative of that photograph and no other images from the photo session.
There are, however, voluminous examples of glamour photography, with thousands of negatives of would-be models and actresses posing in attitudes ranging from chaste portraiture to provocative nudity. Many of these photographs were related to the beauty contests organized by Morehead.
The collection also includes some personal and business papers, as well as books, videotapes, and sound recordings from his personal collection. Of particular interest in the papers is Morehead's correspondence with Playboy, which repeatedly rebuffed his attempts to sell photographs of women of color to the magazine. Also noteworthy are documents pertaining to Morehead's employment at KABC-TV, where he was reprimanded numerous times over the years, eventually prompting him to file a racial-discrimination lawsuit.
Organization and Arrangement
The collection is organized into the following series:
Series 1. Photographs
Series 2. Business and personal papers
Series 3. Video cassettes
Series 4. Sound recordings
Series 5. Scrapbooks
Series 6. Books
Related Online Items Available
Portions of the Howard Morehead photographs and papers have been digitized and are available online: Howard Morehead photographs and papers (182 items)
Photographs.; Beauty contests; Glamour photography; Musicians -- Photographs.; Jazz -- California -- Los Angeles.; Morehead, Howard -- Archives
- Series 1. Photographs, circa 1940-2002
  Scope and Contents note
  This series contains black-and-white and color prints; 35mm, 120, and 3x4 negatives; proof sheets; transparencies.
  - Subseries 1. People, 1947-2002
    Scope and Content
    This subseries contains portraits and candid shots of musicians, actors, politicians, and others.
    - Adams, Joe, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
      2 prints; 21 negatives; proof sheet.
    - Adderley, Cannonball, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
      1 partial proof sheet.
    - Alexander, Monty (with Hassan Shakur), 2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      3 prints; 26 negatives; proof sheet. At Union Station, Los Angeles.
    - Alexandria, Lorez and Clifford Jordan, 1985 and undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
      33 negatives; proof sheets.
    - Ali, Muhammad [Cassius Clay] with Sugar Ray Robinson and Drew Brown, 1964 and undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
      1 print; 75 negatives [print is after first Sonny Liston bout; the negatives may be on the occasion of Ali's final fight in 1981].
    - Anderson, John [trumpet player, with a large jazz ensemble], undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
      24 negatives.
    - Andrews, Ernie et al, undated and 1997 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      1 print; 12 negatives; proof sheets; includes Jackie Mills (drums); program for the memorial service for Dolores Loretta Andrews, Ernie's wife.
    - Andrews, Ernie - oversize print, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Armstrong, Louis and Bing Crosby - oversize print, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Armstrong, Louis and Bing Crosby and Grace Kelly [from High Society], circa 1956 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      2 prints [same image]; negative.
    - Astaire, Fred, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
      2 matted prints [same image]; 22 negatives.
    - Astaire, Fred - oversize matted print, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Bailey, Bob, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
      2 proof sheets.
    - Bailey, Pearl, circa 1954 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      1 print [inscribed by Bailey]; 10 negatives [1 with Robert Mitchum at Ciro's].
    - Baldwin, Sarah [vocalist], 1990 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      14 prints; approximately 500 negatives; proof sheets.
    - Banks, Brenton [violinist], undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
      Matted print.
    - Banks, Brenton - oversize matted print, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Basie, Count, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Basie, Count - oversize matted print, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Basie, Count - foamcore mounted print, undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Belafonte, Harry, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
      1 matted print; 1 negative.
    - Bell, Jean, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
      48 negatives.
    - Bennett, Candace [vocalist], undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
      38 negatives; proof sheet.
    - Benny, Jack and a member of the Lester Horton Dancers, 1957 May 9 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      From Shower of Stars. 1 print.
    - Bibb, Leon, circa 1959 (Box 1, Folder 19)
      150 negatives, some taken at the Ash Grove music club.
    - Blakey, Art, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
      1 print.
    - Boatwright, Colostine "Cookie", 1987 (Box 1, Folder 21)
      107 negatives, proof sheets.
    - Booker, Mease and Tom Kelley [model and photographer], undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
      132 negatives.
    - Bradley, James Jr. [child drumming prodigy], undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
      112 negatives.
    - Bradley, Tom, undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
      2 matted prints [same image]
    - Bradley, Tom and Gilbert Lindsay, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
      36 negatives.
    - Brown, Ray and Oscar Peterson, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
      1 proof sheet.
    - Bryant, Clora, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 26)
      95 negatives; proof sheets.
    - Bryant, Joyce, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
      4 negatives.
    - Callender, Red, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
      3 prints of the same image [on tuba]; 4 negatives [on bass].
    - Canelli, Vince, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
      1 matted print.
    - Carr, Georgia, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
      92 negatives. At Slate Bros. Club.
    - Carroll, Diahann, 1959 September 11 (Box 1, Folder 31)
      1 matted print;48 negatives. Negatives are from the Cloister, Los Angeles.
    - Carroll, Diahann with the Andre Previn Trio, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 31a)
    - Chambers, Paul, undated (Box 22, Folder 2a)
      Scope and Contents
    - Champion, Mickey, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
      52 negatives; proof sheets.
    - Charles, Ray, undated and 1988 (Box 1, Folder 33)
      4 prints; 5 matted prints; CD longbox for Just Between Us.
    - Charles, Ray - oversize matted print, circa 1988 (Box 19)
    - Charles, Ray - oversize, 1964 and undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
      3 matted prints.
    - Charles, Ray - foamcore matted print, undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Coburn, James, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
      2 matted prints [same image]; 6 negatives.
    - Cochlin, Frank, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Collins, Bill - oversize matted print, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Cooper, Leroy, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Cosby, Bill - matted print, undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Counce, Curtis [with quintet], undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Craver, Sonny, undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
      2 prints; 12 negatives; proof sheet.
    - Crawford, Cindy, undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
      2 prints; proof sheets.
    - Crawford, Hank with Phil Upchurch and Marlena Shaw, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 40)
      66 negatives; proof sheets.
    - Crothers, Scatman, undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
      8 negatives; proof sheet.
    - Dandridge, Dorothy, undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
      21 negatives.
    - Daniels, Billy, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Daniels, John, circa 1959 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      204 negatives, with several different musical acts posing and playing. Date etrapolated from the display of the Johnny Mathis album Heavenly.
    - Darrin, Diana, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
      37 negatives.
    - Davis, Miles - foamcore matted print, undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Davis, Miles with Philly Joe Jones, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Davis, Sammy Jr, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      Matted print; negative [different image].
    - Davis, Sammy Jr. - oversize matted print, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Davis, Wild Bill with Crazy Chris Columbo, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
      33 negatives; proof sheets. Also includes an unidentified guitarist and a white guy with a bottle of Manischewitz wine.
    - Dillard, Mimi, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
      59 negatives.
    - Dixon, Allan [vocalist], undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
      8 negatives.
    - Dixon, Floyd, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      20 prints; 134 negatives; concert program.
    - Dougan, Vikki, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
      3 negatives.
    - Dunham, Katherine, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      Performance of Bamboche! at the Huntington Hartford Theatre, Los Angeles. 216 negatives.
    - Eckstine, Billy - foamcore matted print, undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Edison, Harry "Sweets", undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
      2 prints [same image].
    - Edwards, Ella [aka Ellaraino], undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
      28 negatives.
    - Edwards, Teddy et al, undated and 1990-1998 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      20 transparencies; approximately 800 negatives; proof sheets.
    - Eisenhower, Dwight, undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Ellington, Duke and Mahalia Jackson - oversize matted print, undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Ennis, Ethel, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
      47 negatives.
    - Epps, Preston, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Farmer, Art, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      2 prints; 38 negatives.
    - Feather, Leonard with The Sound of Feeling, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
      114 negatives.
    - The 5th Dimension, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
      Approximately 230 negatives. Though not credited to Morehead, the image on the band's Wikipedia page on 5/2/23 is clearly from this photo session. That image is dated 1969 November 20.
    - Fleming, Carolyn, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
      Approximately 336 negatives.
    - Fletcher, Sam [vocalist], 1985-1995 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      60 negatives; proof sheets.
    - Fletcher, Sam - oversize matted print, undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Ford, Gerald - oversize, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 11)
      1 matted print; 1 collage.
    - Ford, Gerald [with Morehead], undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
      Matted print, inscribed by Ford.
    - Foxx. Redd, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
      92 negatives; proof sheet fragment; 1 matted print.
    - Gibson, Althea [in a shoe store], undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
      5 negatives.
    - Gillespie, Dizzy - foamcore matted print, undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
      Biography/History
      The old inventory said this was from the Lighthouse night club.
    - Goodman, Benny - oversize matted print, undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Goodman, Benny - foamcore matted print, undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Gordon, Dexter, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Gordon, Dexter - foamcore matted print, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Gracen, Thelma, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
      20 negatives.
    - Grant, Earl [and others on the set of Club Checkerboard], circa 1958 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      Approximately 340 negatives.
    - Gregory, Dick [and unidentified female vocalist], undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Grindell, Marion [Los Angeles County commissioner], 1968 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Hancock, Hunter, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
      14 negatives.
    - Harlem Globetrotters, undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
      15 negatives.
    - Hartman, Ena, undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
      84 negatives.
    - Hawkins, Tramaine, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 32)
      2 prints; 45 negatives; proof sheets.
    - Henry, Ann [vocalist], undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
      Approximately 180 negatives.
    - "Herman" [young boy], undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Hernandez, Juano, circa 1958 (Box 2, Folder 35)
      Approximately 150 negatives.
      At his Lyceum of Dramatic Art, 8553 Sunset Blvd.
    - The Hi-Fis with Ray Charles, circa 1964 (Box 2, Folder 36)
      Approximately 75 negatives.
      This is a predecessor to The 5th Dimension, with Ray Charles producing.
    - Higgins, Billy, undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Holiday, Billie [with Bobby Troup and Frank Morgan], circa 1957 (Box 2, Folder 38)
      1 print; 5 negatives; proof sheet [though Holiday appears on the proof sheet, only the negatives of Frank Morgan are present].
    - Holiday, Billie - foamcore matted print, undated (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Hopkins, Linda, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Houzell, Paul [artist], undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
      3 prints; 36 negatives; proof sheet.
    - Hunt, Carol and Ann-Marie Sayers, undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
      Approximately 210 negatives.
    - Hurte, Leroy [conductor], undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
      Approximately 110 negatives.
    - Jackson, Jesse, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      3 proof sheets.
    - Jesse Jackson - oversize matted print, undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Jackson, Mahalia, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
      1 print [with Gordon Currie]; 6 negatives [with Duke Ellington].
    - Jacquet, Illinois - matted print, undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Jenkins, Gordon, circa 1964 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Approximately 84 negatives.
      Recording session for Gordon Jenkins Presents My Wife the Blues Singer.
    - Jo, Damita, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
      96 negatives.
    - John, Little Willie, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
      4 prints [two images]; 2 negatives [different images].
    - Jones, January [vocalist, not the Mad Men actress], undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
      60 negatives.
    - Jones, Jerry [vocalist], 1995 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      3 prints; approximately 400 negatives; proof sheets.
    - Jordan, Louis [with unidentified woman], undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Kamela, Lahaina, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      74 negatives.
    - Kennedy, John F., 1960 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      Campaigning for president on the 4000 block of Central Ave. in Los Angeles.
    - Kennedy, John F. - matted print, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Kido, Caroline, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
      Approximately 80 negatives.
    - King, Martin Luther Jr., undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
      3 proof sheets [all for the same 24 negatives, which are not present].
    - Kitt, Eartha - oversize matted print, undated (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Kitt, Eartha, undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Land, Harold, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
      62 negatives; proof sheets.
    - Land, Harold - oversize matted print, undated (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - LaRue, Florence, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
      Approximately 170 negatives.
    - Lawrence, Mittie, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
      Approximately 900 negatives.
    - Leung, Mei Ling, circa 1960 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Lewis, Jerry [with Lionel Hampton], 1960 (Box 4, Folder 17)
      69 negatives.
      These photos are from Lewis's 1960 Timex special on NBC, when most of Hampton's appearance was cut for time.
    - Lewis, Ramsey, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Limyou, Jeanna, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
      144 negatives.
    - Lindsay, Gilbert - oversize matted print, undated (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Little Richard, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Lloyd, Charles, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 21)
      7 prints; approximately 160 negatives; proof sheets.
    - Lloyd, Charles - oversize print, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Lutcher, Nellie, undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Lynn, Gloria, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 23)
      3 prints; approximately 100 negatives; proof sheets.
    - Lynn, Gloria - oversize, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 18)
      2 matted prints.
    - Mabley, Moms [with Tom Smothers Brothers and Eddie Albert], 1967 (Box 4, Folder 24)
      144 negatives. Performing a Pinocchio sketch on the Smothers Brothers Comedy Hour, Season 2, Episode 7.
    - Mandela, Nelson, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      1 print; 2 matted prints [all have the same image].
    - Mansfield, Jayne, undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Martin, Dean, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Martin, Dean - oversize matted print, undated (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Matthews, Onzy et al, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - McCann, Les, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 28)
      1 print; 1 proof sheet.
    - McLin, Claude et al, undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - McNair, Barbara, undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
      57 negatives.
    - Meredith, Burgess - matted print, undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Mitchell, Don et al, undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Mitchell, Herman [guitarist], undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Monk, Thelonious, undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
      2 matted prints [same image].
      The old inventory said this was from the Monterey Jazz Festival.
    - Moore, Archie, undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Morgan, Frank, circa 1997 (Box 4, Folder 34)
      6 prints; approximately 475 negatives; proof sheets.
    - Morrison, Barbara, 1998-2000 (Box 4, Folder 35)
      21 stills; 4 transparencies; approximately 180 negatives; proof sheets; Morrison's resume.
    - Mulligan, Gerry - matted print, undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Murray, Rev. Cecil - oversize matted print, undated (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Nichols, Nichelle, undated (Box 4, Folder 35a)
      1 8x10 print.
    - Nobumoto, Lisa [vocalist], undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
      2 prints.
    - The Obsessions [female trio], undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
      70 negatives.
    - Parker, Charlie - oversize, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Parker, Charlie and Larance Marable, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Parker, Dolores [vocalist], undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Approximately 175 negatives.
      Some are shot on the set of Club Checkerboard and some are at Ben Blue's in Santa Monica.
    - Powell, Bud, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      1 matted partial print; 9 negatives.
    - Powell, Bud - oversize print, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Poyand, Bill, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Pratts, Yvonne [vocalist], undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Price, Ruth, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
      5 prints; 57 negatives; proof sheets.
    - Price, Vincent and a member of the Lester Horton Dancers, 1957 May 9 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Prowse, Juliet, undated (Box 5, Folder 7a)
      2 8x10 prints (1 image).
    - Prude, Terrell [pianist], undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
      2 prints; 37 negatives; proof sheets.
    - Prudhomme Twins, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Pryor, Richard - oversize matted print, undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Randolph, Lillian, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
      6 negatives.
    - Razaf, Andy, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
      36 negatives; proof sheets.
    - Redd, Vi, undated and 2001 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      3 prints; 18 transparencies; 114 negatives; proof sheets.
    - Robbins, Rene [vocalist], undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
      110 negatives.
    - Robeson, Paul, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      1 photo collage.
    - Robeson, Paul - oversize, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      2 mounted photo collages [same image].
    - Robinson, Pearl [some with Sam Yorty], 1960 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      108 negatives. Robinson was Miss Bronze California, 1960.
    - Roosevelt, Eleanor, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
      1 negative.
    - Rubalcaba, Gonzalo, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      2 prints; 55 negatives; proof sheets.
    - Russell, Gene, undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
      9 negatives.
    - Sampson, Jean, undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Sheen, Tony, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      3 prints; 37 negatives; proof sheet.
    - Short, Bobby, undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Simon, Maurice [with quartet at dance party], undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Sinatra, Frank, undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
      1 print; 1 negative.
    - Sinatra, Frank - foamcore matted print, undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Smith, Camilla, undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Smith, Jimmy, 1984-1997 (Box 5, Folder 25)
      4 prints; approximately 250 negatives; proof sheets.
    - Smith, O.C., undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Stitt, Sonny, undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
      Approximately 250 negatives.
    - Sullivan, Niki [with band], undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Sweet Baby J'ai, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
      1 print; 36 negatives; proof sheet.
    - Sylvers, Shirley, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Talbert, Norma [showgirl], undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
      12 negatives.
      Talbert worked at the Moulin Rouge in Las Vegas, the first integrated casino in the country.
    - Taylor, Joyce, undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Torme, Mel and George Shearing, undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - The Treniers, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 34)
      Approximately 110 negatives. At the Moulin Rouge, Las Vegas.
    - Turner, Jean with Stan Kenton and others, undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
      Approximately 100 negatives.